[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Again, it's all a bit pathetic, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Again", ",", "it", "'s", "all", "a", "bit", "pathetic", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Do you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "How do you change the culture so that at the very least you can start to put some kind of controls on these types of people legally buying assault weapons and so on?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "change", "the", "culture", "so", "that", "at", "the", "very", "least", "you", "can", "start", "to", "put", "some", "kind", "of", "controls", "on", "these", "types", "of", "people", "legally", "buying", "assault", "weapons", "and", "so", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "I honestly don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "honestly", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "Well, what are they afraid of?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "are", "they", "afraid", "of", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "They're afraid of a public that wants to have its guns.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "afraid", "of", "a", "public", "that", "wants", "to", "have", "its", "guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "Why doesn't he have the balls to do it on something like this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "does", "n't", "he", "have", "the", "balls", "to", "do", "it", "on", "something", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "He just never has on this issue as a national candidate and it's a real defect in him.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "just", "never", "has", "on", "this", "issue", "as", "a", "national", "candidate", "and", "it", "'s", "a", "real", "defect", "in", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Frank, very quickly, one word or one name, who's your current favorite for VP for Romney?", "question_tokens": ["Frank", ",", "very", "quickly", ",", "one", "word", "or", "one", "name", ",", "who", "'s", "your", "current", "favorite", "for", "VP", "for", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "CC", "CD", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "ICH: Whom I want or --", "answer_tokens": ["ICH", ":", "Whom", "I", "want", "or", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Portman"], "LOCATION": ["Pawlenty"]}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "VBZ", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "VBG", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Who's the most likely boring white guy?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "the", "most", "likely", "boring", "white", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Well, the most boring is Portman but the second most boring is Pawlenty.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "most", "boring", "is", "Portman", "but", "the", "second", "most", "boring", "is", "Pawlenty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Starbucks"]}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Why is this right for Starbucks?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "this", "right", "for", "Starbucks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Over the past year or so when we introduced mobile payments at Starbucks, we have never seen anything adopted so quickly.", "answer_tokens": ["Over", "the", "past", "year", "or", "so", "when", "we", "introduced", "mobile", "payments", "at", "Starbucks", ",", "we", "have", "never", "seen", "anything", "adopted", "so", "quickly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Starbucks"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "That's it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "That's eventually it.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "eventually", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "What's the end game?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "end", "game", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Well, we believe in simplifying the very complex.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "believe", "in", "simplifying", "the", "very", "complex", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Why do I need this in my life?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "I", "need", "this", "in", "my", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "I think it's -- I think it's more added to what you can do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "--", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "more", "added", "to", "what", "you", "can", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Starbucks"], "PERCENT": ["25 percent"]}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "How many of your customers, do you think, will, say in five years' time, potentially be using Square to buy coffee?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "of", "your", "customers", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "will", ",", "say", "in", "five", "years", "'", "time", ",", "potentially", "be", "using", "Square", "to", "buy", "coffee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "MD", ",", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "POS", "NN", ",", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Already 25 percent of all of our customers are using the Starbucks card.", "answer_tokens": ["Already", "25", "percent", "of", "all", "of", "our", "customers", "are", "using", "the", "Starbucks", "card", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Could that happen?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "that", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "I love -- I love that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "--", "I", "love", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Why shouldn't it be like that really?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "n't", "it", "be", "like", "that", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "I think it -- I wouldn't say that's not possible.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "--", "I", "would", "n't", "say", "that", "'s", "not", "possible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "I mean what is the -- what is the right call for America?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "what", "is", "the", "--", "what", "is", "the", "right", "call", "for", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "I'm not here to call the presidency, I appreciate the question.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "here", "to", "call", "the", "presidency", ",", "I", "appreciate", "the", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "What is the answer to America incorporated?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "answer", "to", "America", "incorporated", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "We have to give people simple tools that they can define a new reality and a new destiny.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "to", "give", "people", "simple", "tools", "that", "they", "can", "define", "a", "new", "reality", "and", "a", "new", "destiny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Rather than the cheaper route of making them in the Far East?", "question_tokens": ["Rather", "than", "the", "cheaper", "route", "of", "making", "them", "in", "the", "Far", "East", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Far East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "When you're a new fledgling company like this and it grows so fast, so quickly this kind of issue is going to throw up all kinds of ethical dilemmas that you have to wrestle with, right?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "'re", "a", "new", "fledgling", "company", "like", "this", "and", "it", "grows", "so", "fast", ",", "so", "quickly", "this", "kind", "of", "issue", "is", "going", "to", "throw", "up", "all", "kinds", "of", "ethical", "dilemmas", "that", "you", "have", "to", "wrestle", "with", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "They've done a very good job.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'ve", "done", "a", "very", "good", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Do you tweet?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "tweet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "CHULTZ: I do not.", "answer_tokens": ["CHULTZ", ":", "I", "do", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "JJR", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Why don't you tweet?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "you", "tweet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "I have so much going on in my life that I feel if I add one more thing, I don't have the time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "so", "much", "going", "on", "in", "my", "life", "that", "I", "feel", "if", "I", "add", "one", "more", "thing", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "How much of the problem has been also cultural issues of people just wanting a fast buck, perhaps not wanting to put the graft that their fore bearers put in?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "the", "problem", "has", "been", "also", "cultural", "issues", "of", "people", "just", "wanting", "a", "fast", "buck", ",", "perhaps", "not", "wanting", "to", "put", "the", "graft", "that", "their", "fore", "bearers", "put", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "I don't put the burden on the American people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "put", "the", "burden", "on", "the", "American", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "At all?", "question_tokens": ["At", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "What is the answer?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "How about America get a grip with its current state of depression and let's discuss that first, because the gun really isn't the problem.", "answer_tokens": ["How", "about", "America", "get", "a", "grip", "with", "its", "current", "state", "of", "depression", "and", "let", "'s", "discuss", "that", "first", ",", "because", "the", "gun", "really", "is", "n't", "the", "problem", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "I'm not going to go out and blow somebody up, but why can't we change the way we allow people to buy them?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "go", "out", "and", "blow", "somebody", "up", ",", "but", "why", "ca", "n't", "we", "change", "the", "way", "we", "allow", "people", "to", "buy", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "NN", "NN", "IN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "I agree totally with everything you've just said.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "agree", "totally", "with", "everything", "you", "'ve", "just", "said", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Why can't I find out if you're visiting a psychiatrist or a psychologist?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "ca", "n't", "I", "find", "out", "if", "you", "'re", "visiting", "a", "psychiatrist", "or", "a", "psychologist", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Why is it the media within a few hours of this latest atrocity of the Sikh temple are able to find out so much information about the shooter.", "answer_tokens": ["Why", "is", "it", "the", "media", "within", "a", "few", "hours", "of", "this", "latest", "atrocity", "of", "the", "Sikh", "temple", "are", "able", "to", "find", "out", "so", "much", "information", "about", "the", "shooter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Why can't we do that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "ca", "n't", "we", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "I completely agree.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "completely", "agree", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "WP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "CC", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Where do we meet to make America a better place?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "we", "meet", "to", "make", "America", "a", "better", "place", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "That's the deal, but guess what, unfortunately, the main people who are in charge of this whole process in the country, the first three letters of the constitution, we the people have laid over and played dead.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "deal", ",", "but", "guess", "what", ",", "unfortunately", ",", "the", "main", "people", "who", "are", "in", "charge", "of", "this", "whole", "process", "in", "the", "country", ",", "the", "first", "three", "letters", "of", "the", "constitution", ",", "we", "the", "people", "have", "laid", "over", "and", "played", "dead", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "What's your thinking on this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "thinking", "on", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Please don't let me polarize more people.", "answer_tokens": ["Please", "do", "n't", "let", "me", "polarize", "more", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "How long have you had MS now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "long", "have", "you", "had", "MS", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "If we go by diagnosis, it's my 13th year.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "we", "go", "by", "diagnosis", ",", "it", "'s", "my", "13th", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "You're going to be doing this heliboard?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "going", "to", "be", "doing", "this", "heliboard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "This is my 13th anniversary with MS, I have been working.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "my", "13th", "anniversary", "with", "MS", ",", "I", "have", "been", "working", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]